

Mohamed Amin Sedki

CONTACT



+971502577354



moamsed@gmail.com



n Dubai, UAE

PROFILE

I Seek to Apply The Experiences and Skills Gained Githin The Competitive Work Environment to Enhance my Ability to progress and Refine my Skills as well as to Find The Right Environment to Acquire New Experiences and Skills to promote The School in which i work At The Top

LANGUAGES

Arabic - Native English - Basic

WORK EXPERIENCE

Educational materials designer Al hayat center July 2018 - Nov 2019

DATA ENTRY Al-alhafez cosmetics Dec 2019- May 2020

computer teacher Al-Manar Islamic Schools Aug 2020- june 2020

EDUCATION

MINIA UNIVERSITY 2015 - 2019 Faculty of Specific Education Specialty Education Technology

PERSONAL INFO

Date of Birth: 4/9/1997 Marital Status: UNmarried

Gender: male Religion: Muslim

SOFTWARE SKILLS

MICROSOFT OFFICE

WORD ACCESS

EXCEL **POWER POINT**

ADOBE

PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR

PERSONAL SKILLS

WORK UNDER PRESSURE **CONSTANT PASSION** COMMITMENT AND ORDER **CONTINUOUS LEARNING** INTELLIGENCE